http://explorerventures.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
HomePrivacy Policy
EXPLORER VENTURES (USA) LTD. PRIVACY POLICY
Explorer Ventures (USA) Ltd. and Explorer Ventures Ltd. ("us", "we" or "our) are committed to protecting your personal information that you share and want to tell you know how we manage the information we receive. By browsing and using our website you agree to this policy governing your use of the website. If you do not accept this policy, you should not use our website.
We collect information about you through two principal means: through technology (for example IP addresses and cookies) and through your voluntary submission of information.
How does Explorer Ventures keep information private?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.
Will I get emails I don’t want?
We send regular emails to our Agents/Customers who opted in for these emails.
If you wish to opt out and unsubscribe, you may do so at any time by emailing info@explorerventures.com or by clicking on the Unsubscribe link on the bottom of the email.
What information does Explorer Ventures (USA) Ltd collect?
When you sign up for promotional emails or contact customer support via the Chat function on our website, we collect your name and email address.
When making a reservation and/or as part of the booking process, as appropriate, we ask for the following information: name, gender, dive experience, height and weight, email address, phone number, passport information, emergency contact, trip insurance, scuba certification, citizenship and special reservation requests, such as diet preferences and sizes of diving gear rentals. We also ask for any medical history which we need to be aware of during your stay with us.
Is my information safe?
We use a secure server. All sensitive information supplied is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology, and is only accessible to those authorized with special access rights to such systems, who are required to keep the information confidential.
Even with all the measures we take, we cannot guarantee the protection of your personal information and/or use of our sites in situations beyond our control (force majeure), such as hacking attacks.
Our use of Cookies
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Questions or Comments?
If you have would like to access, correct, amend, or delete any personal information and/or if you have questions or comments, please feel free to email info@explorerventures.com.
Stay Connected Sign up for our newsletter!
From last minute booking specials to promotional dive packages, special events and news, it will keep you in touch with what we're doing!
How did you first learn about Explorer Ventures?---Green Fins/The Reef-World FoundationDive or Trade ShowInternet SearchAd on GoogleFacebookInstagramTwitterYouTubeScubaBoardScuba Diver LifeSport DiverScuba Diving MagazineDive Training MagazineDiver UK MagazineAlert DiverDive GuideDive Center Business MagazineUndercurrentScubaRadioCruisers AcademyEV NewsletterLocal Shop/AgentWord of mouth/friendOther
Sign me up for your mailing list
Upcoming Dive Shows
Explorer Ventures will be at the following dive shows:
Beneath the Sea, Seacaucus, NJ,&nbspMarch 12-14, 2021,  Booth 717
DIVE 2020, Birmingham, UK,&nbspMar. 27-28, 2021,  Booth 210
ADEX, Singapore,&nbspApril 9-11, 2021,  Booth D16
Scuba Show, Long Beach, CA,&nbspMay 22-23, 2021,  Booth TBD
DEMA Show 2021, Las Vegas, NV,&nbspNovember 16-19, 2021,  Booth 1049
Dive Green
Explorer Ventures © 2020 • Site Designed by Duck Diver, LLC.
×
Turks & Caicos Explorer II
VIP Staterooms: Queen bed, desk/chair, hanging closet, wardrobe, large window, TV, private ensuite bathroom and shower (couple only).
Staterooms 1-2.
$2,895
Main Deck Staterooms: Twin or Queen bed, desk/chair, hanging closet, wardrobe, large window(s), private ensuite bathroom and shower.
Staterooms 3-4, twins. Staterooms 5-7, queen or twins.
$2,695
Lower Deck Staterooms: Twin lower and upper beds, dresser, hanging closet, port lights, private ensuite bathroom and shower. Staterooms 8-10.
$2,495
Plus: port/hotel tax of $95 and fuel surcharge payable on board; transfers. Package includes: 7 nights/8 days aboard the vessel; up to 5 dives daily (weather permitting);
3 meals daily, except Friday's evening meal; between-dive snacks; towels, linens, etc.; use of tanks, weights and weight belts; all air fills; alcohol and non-alcoholic beverages.
Close
×
Caribbean Explorer II
All Staterooms: On main and lower decks, each with private in suite bathroom and shower.
$2,095/pp
Additional Charges include: port/hotel, immigration and Marine Park fees of $115 and fuel surcharge payable on board; transfers. Package includes: 7 nights/8 days aboard the vessel; up to 5 dives daily (weather permitting);
3 meals daily, except Friday's evening meal; between-dive snacks; towels, linens, etc.; use of tanks, weights and weight belts; all air fills; alcohol and non-alcoholic beverages.
Close
×
Sign Up and Dive In
Signing up will be your best decision ever! By subscribing to our free monthly email, you will be the first in line to receive our exclusive diving offers. Plus, you'll stay up to date on our Fleet with latest news, curated articles, featured videos, and more.
Country United StatesCanadaAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaireBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet Island (Bouvetoya)BrazilBritish Indian Ocean Territory (Chagos Archipelago)British Virgin IslandsBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongoCongoCook IslandsCosta RicaCote d'IvoireCroatiaCubaCuracaoCyprusCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas)Faroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard Island and McDonald IslandsHoly See (Vatican City State)HondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKoreaKoreaKuwaitKyrgyz RepublicLao People's Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyan Arab JamahiriyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacaoMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoryPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairn IslandsPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarReunionRomaniaRussian FederationRwandaSaint BarthelemySaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint MartinSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint Maarten (Netherlands)Slovakia (Slovak Republic)SloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia & S. Sandwich IslandsSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard & Jan Mayen IslandsSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyrian Arab RepublicTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluU.S. Virgin IslandsU.S. Minor Outlying IslandsUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamWallis and FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabwe
How did you first learn about Explorer Ventures?---Green Fins/The Reef-World FoundationDive or Trade ShowInternet SearchAd on GoogleFacebookInstagramTwitterYouTubeScubaBoardScuba Diver LifeSport DiverScuba Diving MagazineDive Training MagazineDiver UK MagazineAlert DiverDive GuideDive Center Business MagazineUndercurrentScubaRadioCruisers AcademyEV NewsletterLocal Shop/AgentWord of mouth/friendOther
